export const defaultDeck = {
  title: "50 Most Common Spanish Verbs (Default Deck)",
  description:
    "Get started on your Spanish journey with the 50 most absolutely essential Spanish verbs",
  flashcards: [
    {
      front: "ser",
      back: "to be (essential/permanent quality)",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "haber",
      back: "to have (to do something, auxiliary verb)",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "estar",
      back: "to be (health, location, state)",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "tener", back: "to have", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "hacer", back: "to do, make", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "poder",
      back: "	to be able, can",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "decir", back: "to say, tell", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "ir", back: "to go", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "ver", back: "to see", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "dar", back: "to give", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "saber",
      back: "to know (information)",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "querer", back: "to want, love", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "llegar",
      back: "to arrive, come, reach",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "pasar",
      back: "to pass, to spend (time), to happen",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "deber",
      back: "to owe, must, should, ought to",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "poner",
      back: "to put, place, set",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "parecer",
      back: "to seem, appear",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "quedar",
      back: "to stay, remain",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "creer", back: "to believe", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "hablar", back: "to speak", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "llevar",
      back: "to carry, bring",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "dejar",
      back: "to leave, abandon, to let, allow",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "seguir",
      back: "to follow, continue",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "encontrar",
      back: "to find, encounter",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "llamar",
      back: "to call, to name",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "venir", back: "to come", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "pensar", back: "to think", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "salir",
      back: "to leave, go out",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "volver",
      back: "to return, go back",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "tomar", back: "to take, drink", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "conocer",
      back: "to know (people, places)",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "vivir", back: "to live", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "sentir",
      back: "to feel, regret",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "tratar",
      back: "to treat, handle",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "mirar",
      back: "to watch, look at",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "contar",
      back: "to count, relate, tell",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "empezar",
      back: "to begin, start",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "esperar",
      back: "to wait for, to hope",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "buscar",
      back: "to search for, look for",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "existir", back: "to exist", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "entrar",
      back: "to enter, go in, come in",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    { front: "trabajar", back: "to work", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "escribir", back: "to write", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "perder", back: "to lose", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    { front: "producir", back: "to produce", lastReviewed: null, strength: 0 },
    {
      front: "ocurrir",
      back: "to occur/happen",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "entender",
      back: "to understand",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "pedir",
      back: "to request, ask for",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "recibir",
      back: "to receive, to welcome, greet",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
    {
      front: "recordar",
      back: "to remember, remind",
      lastReviewed: null,
      strength: 0,
    },
  ].map((card, index) => ({ ...card, id: index })),
};
